Uh-huh.
Yes, sir.
Yes, please.
There's an ad for a shave.
Ad for a shave.
Gomaybah.
Gomaiva.
Terrace Mall Shonan
The one in Tsujido.
I don't know.
Good evening.
The master has started.
After all, we're here for one-shot.
Let's do a gag.
Let's do that one.
That one...
That one!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Messy.
Let's go! Let's go!
So, everyone, today we're delivering an hour early, right?
I know... but... well...
It looks like she's back from Thailand.
You know exactly what I mean.
I see. First of all, let me proceed with the program.
Yes, that's right.
So, let's begin.
Let's begin. Let's get started.
Let's begin.
Yes, without any reason.
Yes.
Today is already the 22nd of December?
Oh, it's eve eve eve.
Christmas eve eve eve.
Oh, I'm so busy this Christmas already this year.
Yes.
Well, you know, you know...
I've been, you know, you know...
I'm roasting a turkey,
Yes.
And..,
I don't know, opening a bottle of champagne,
Yeah, and some kind of cake, yes.
A Christmas cake, yes. Cutting it,
That's nice. Cutting.
I'm so busy every year.
Yes, it's a lot of work. How about you two? What about Christmas?
Hahahahahaha!
How is it? What?
You won't touch me! Touch me!
You won't touch me. Touch me!
How are you doing? Are you working or something? See you later.
Is it Christmas? Yes, it is.
Well, well, well, well. I'm working.
Really, though, especially these days, you know, there are many tourist spots in this area. Yes, that's right.
As Christmas approaches, the ratio of couples is increasing. Oh, no. Already the ratio of couples as Christmas approaches. I mean, it's already.
I think it's about 77% right now. Is that right?
If there are 100 people, 77 of them are couples. If there are 100 people, 77 of them are couples? Yes, that's right.
What's that result?
I'm just saying. I'm just saying that. Today is December 22nd, which means, in case you were wondering, today is the....
Winter Solstice! Winter Solstice!
Let's close the winter!
Oh, it's over, isn't it?
Winter Solstice!
It's over!
I see... I thought it was just the beginning.
Yes, let's close it up.
This year ended without anything wintery, winter?
Yes, it was a little cold.
Does that mean it will start to look like spring tomorrow?
That's early!
It's not even the beginning of the year yet.
Well, you see, climate change!
Yes, yes, yes.
That's what you wanted to say!
I see!
That's exactly what
By global warming.
Yes, that's right.
Winter Solstice like the Winter Solstice
has become like the winter solstice.
Actually, the winter solstice is the lowest day of the year
In the northern hemisphere, the sun is at its lowest point of the year.
So the day is the shortest and the night is the longest.
Longest night Long
On this day, take a yuzu bath with yuzu floating in it
It is said that if you eat pumpkin, you will not catch a cold
eat it
Let's eat
It brings back memories of Yuzu-yu
We do Yuzu-yu, don't we?
Do you do it in Saeki, too? Yuzuyu?
Yes, we do.
That's right.
It's also Soup Day
December 22nd.
Let's see...
December is always the month of December.
It's like this...
Always like this
Right?
That's why it's Soup Day!
By the way, there are three major soups in the world
French bouillabaisse
Shark's fin soup in China
And that one in Thailand!
Yes, I know what it is.
Tom Yam Kung.
There are many kinds of soups.
These are the three most common.
Another famous one is clam chowder.
I love it!
Minestrone
Delicious! Delicious
Corn Soup
My favorite
Onion Soup
With cheese!
Oh, it's so good!
Miso soup?
It's not soup? I think it's miso soup, but there's not much in it.
What's your favorite soup? Oh, I like that one. Sweet potato and corn soup.
What is that? Original? Original? They sell it in the store. What's it called?
Sweet potato and corn soup. It's so delicious, it reminds me of autumn.
What? Is it in a convenience store? It's from a place called Soup Stock.
The fancy ones? Yes, it's a fancy soup shop.
Yeah, there's a place called Fireworks Daily.
I'm doing a daily. Are you okay? I'm fine. I'm fine.
It's okay. - It's okay? Anyone can come in. It's just...
Oh, yeah?
I'm kind of laying it out there.
I'm a little nervous there myself.
There are a lot of women here, so there are a lot of women alone.
It's like a women's car. Men can't go there at all.
Well, well, well, well. What's your favorite soup, by the way?
Clam chowder. I like it with crackers.
Clam chowder is good, isn't it? The kind with clams?
That's right, the clam chowder.
I really like the clam chowder at Costco.
It's delicious.
Clam chowder for sure!
That's why you wrote to me.
I'd like to go there. I'd like to go there.
This is just a little bit like that.
Hell's Army K. Kawasaki-ward, Kawasaki-city
Thank you very much.
Master Sarpon, Mr. Ebichu, Good evening, Devil!
The doll that Mr. Cocoon gave to Mr. Balekikata as a birthday present...
I found it in the crane game at the arcade in a chaotic state.
And so...
Aggree baby girl!
Ugly Baby!
Yes, yes, yes...
I'm afraid it's a little bit scary... a little bit of an aggregate... a little bit of an aggregate...
Excuse me, just a minute, please...
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry...
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry
And this is a nice picture, but this time of year there aren't many fireworks displays.
It's a summer image, isn't it?
Thank you very much. I saw the winter fireworks in Tokyo the other day.
It was very short, only 5 minutes, but it was great to see the fireworks with the beautiful night view.
I was wondering if there are any places you would like to go and see the fireworks in this season because it's getting colder.
So first of all, let me show you some pictures.
It looks like this. Wow, it's so beautiful.
It looks like a painting. -A painting?
Is this a picture? You're really good at taking pictures.
Yes, very good.
It's like an afterimage.
But I guess it's easier to see because the air is cleaner.
It's so beautiful.
Rainbow Bridge looks like a rainbow!
It really is a rainbow! It really is a rainbow.
You can see the beautiful Tokyo Tower.
Thank you very much.
Is there a place you want to go now that it's cold?
I think I went to Hokkaido last year.
Hokkaido in winter is nice.
It was the first time I saw snow in Hokkaido.
It was a lot of fun.
It was really cold, though.
As someone who likes to travel said...
It's cold in some areas, right?
It's better when it's cold.
And food, too.
Hot areas are best when it's hot.
Hokkaido in winter is great. Summer is great, too.
I just can't get enough of the locals... the Hokkaido people...
You know how locals in Hokkaido wear so light? In winter, they wear T-shirts.
They don't go outside. But Hokkaido people stay inside.
But people in Hokkaido wear a t-shirt and a down jacket because it gets too hot with the heater.
I've seen a lot of people in short sleeves at bars and bars, and I thought, "Wow, they're locals!
So they go to the corner with down jackets like a t-shirt.
It seems to be Hokkaido, right?
Hokkaido is very cold, isn't it?
And this is good, too
And this is good too, a signboard, a signboard, a signboard
a signboard, or a signboard, or a signboard, or a signboard, or a signboard, or a signboard, or a signboard, or something like that
Thank you a I found this kind of pop-up at a supermarket.
I found this kind of pop-up in a supermarket, so I took a picture of it without thinking.
What a curry concentration stew!
Cute, you must have chewed it, right? I'm sure you chewed it, right?
I'm going to go in there and concentrate.
I'm sure you'll get burned if you put curry in the concentration, but it's nice.
I'm sure I'd get burned if I put curry in the concentration.
It's kind of comforting. I'm like that.
I'm a futon maker, but...
They've been in business for a long time.
but the cat on the sign... whoever wrote it... the kid is really good.
It's got a certain taste.
His eyebrows are cut so crisply... and they're made in the city.
It's like they're separated by the city.
It looks very comfortable.
I like it. It's tasteful.
It has a taste.
That's why I'm here.
Let's go to the corner.
Yes.
Creation of creatures.
This is the last one for this year.
Creation.
The last creature creation of the year?
I'll close out the year 2023 with a subject sent to me by our shopping guru, Monopoly.
I've posted it in the "living creature creation" section.
May I? The creature's name... is the Great Pacific Redheaded Monopoly.
Is that far out? From the Pacific? Pacific red-bellied woodpecker.
So...
I don't know what akavo is before akavo. Thank you very much.
What's akabo? What's akabo? Pacific akabo-modoki.
What is it? I'm sure you've seen this one before... but I'm sure you've seen it distributed. What is it? But I'm sure there's something in there, right?
I mean, they're all smart enough to know that, right?
Pacific akavo.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm just a little too smart for that.
Wait a minute.
So many creatures have been born this year.
They've been imagined. Wait a minute.
I'm deeply moved.
What am I writing?
Well, well, well...
It's all right.
Wait a minute.
Pacific Red Hats
I've always wondered...
There are a lot of living creatures that can do that, aren't there?
Yes, they are.
I feel sorry for them, don't you?
Well, there are squid, for example, but squid is famous...
But let's give it a name... "squid" makes it sound like a fake.
Well, if it's discovered too late, it'll be a fake because it's so similar
I'll put it like this around here or something.
Well, I'll go to Thailand and take pictures.
I've already been to Thailand, and I'm on a roll.
And the photo book will be on sale on January 24th.
This way, sir. - Wow, he's going straight to the Pacific.
I'm a red cap who wants to go back to the Pacific.
So you used to live in the Pacific Ocean... but somehow you got a little off the beaten path. So you used to live in the Pacific Ocean?
Mr. Akabo... he's on land or something... and he's struggling.
he's struggling to get back home...
He looks like he wants to go home.
And then the teacher, yes, please...
Cute! What's this? It's kinda cool...
I really didn't get it, but what's that floating in the Pacific? Some kind of bug?
Isn't that a float? It's got a floatation device. It's got a butt.
Oh, I see. I see.
I keep thinking...
It looks like a baby, doesn't it? Like a baby!
I see. It looks like a baby.
Good. - That's for sure. Yes.
I see what you mean. That's great.
No, no, no, no, it's great.
By the way, a Pacific red cap is... like this...
It's a member of the whale family.
It's a fish after all! How should I put it?
It's a bit reddish here...
A red hat... a hat...
- I see... Matsuda, maybe not... Nakamura, yes...
Nakamura
- Nakamura He seems very cute. Nakamura He's cute.
- Nakamura... cute.
Nakamura Yes.
- NakamuraThe last one this year, right?
- Nakamura Yes.
- Thank you, Nakamura.
- So we're here now... Nakamura Yes? - So, here we are, then. Nakamura.
Let's see...
I have an announcement.
Yes?
Um...
As I already told you...
March 31st.
Yes, sir.
Odate Uchidevil
will be held
Yes.
Yes, sir.
And so is Evijucie.
And we'll be there.
All of us...
Well...
It's been a year.
That's right.
We've been through a lot.
Yes.
I'd like to have a lot of fun.
Yes...
Um...
VIP seats S and VIP seats are on sale now.
How are they? Are they on sale now? Are they on sale now? We're taking reservations.
VIP S? VIP S is on sale now.
VIP S is, by the way, the one in the front row.
It's like front row, right in front of you.
Great, a special seat. Dangerous, right there. Wow, that's nice. That's a great seat. It's dangerous, right there.
It's a given that you're a VIP, so we'll give it to you.
We'd like to give the VIPs some color, don't you think?
Yes, we're working on a special gift for visitors.
We're finalizing the gift items for the VIPs.
Great. Let's start with this.
Sakosh! Sakosh?
This is the front. Turn it over and you'll see our poster.
You know, the sash... that we wear here... on our collarbone...
Collarbone?
Hang it like this... like this... So it's called a clavicle.
That's why it's called a clavicle.
You know your stuff.
As one would expect.
Collarbone.
Yes...
And, uh...
So-called VIP's...
S
Yes, sir.
Now, plus...
What a surprise!
Here's a badge.
Here you go.
All of you, plus me and Mr. Sarpong.
All of them?
All of them? All of them!
Wow, it's like a film here.
It's like a film, and you can put them all here. It's like a film, and you can arrange everything here like this.
You can put them in here? Wow, amazing!
It's really nice.
It's heavy, so it's a little heavy on the collarbone.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm sure you'll be impressed.
Wow, amazing! Gorgeous!
This mayama is so cute.
Look at this.
So cute!
I have to buy it.
And the Hanamichi version, too.
I just got the sample.
Yes, it's been in the works for a while now, but it will come with that, too.
This is it, isn't it?
VIP!
If you buy it, we'll give you this sash.
If you become an "S", you also get this badge.
It's so great that everyone who had a front-row conversation with me was interested in my collarbone.
I'm so happy!
Why are you still accepting orders?
I'm sure everyone in the front row is interested in your clavicles.
Please check out A-Man's website.
Ara-chan, it's almost this Sunday!
I'm going to go to an orthopedist first, then I'll reinforce the clavicle.
I'm not saying that... but... when we first started talking about the building in Odate...
When we started talking about the building in Odate, I thought it would be on the 31st of March next spring, but it'll be soon, it's only a matter of time.
And isn't this the last day of high school? March 31st, that's right.
March 31st is the last day of high school... and the last day of graduation. School's out, graduation's in session, and it's my last day of high school.
Last day of high school. I'm going to go out with a bang.
You're going? You're going?
Wow! I don't know.
Yeah, well, by all means, Mike, I'll ride with you.
Get your license! First of all, no.
But I don't understand... can I drive on private property? Well, there's a security guard on duty.
But don't, it's really dangerous.
I'm not safe...
And as I was saying, today's live broadcast...
Thank you for watching.
This is the last Canada Devil broadcast before the end of the year.
The last one before the end of the year.
I'm sure you'll enjoy it.
Um...
Well...
We'll still have the live broadcast of "Devil's coming, Devil's going" before the end of the year.
I hope to see you there as well.
We'll be broadcasting live on youtube next week as well.
We'll be filming the beginning of the new year.
We'll be filming the beginning of the new year and stuff.
We don't do that much sometimes... but only 1 or 2 weeks...
When we talk about the future, it makes me feel like I'm an adult.
I'm so impressed that I'm an adult.
They talk about down jackets in the middle of summer.
They do shoots in the middle of summer.
I'm glad. That's all I have to say.
The last thing...
I made it back alive from Thailand... so I'm going to start with the flower arrangement...
I'll probably do the Hanamichi for the last time this year, so have a Happy New Year and take care of yourselves. This will probably be the last Hanamichi show of the year, so have a Happy New Year and take good care of yourselves.
I don't know what you're talking about. Take care of yourself.
Have a happy new year. Thank you. Five minutes.
Five minutes...
Five minutes. Five minutes. Five minutes.
Well, well, well, well... So, that's why... the paper goes down with a thud.
Yes, that's right. What's wrong?
I'll see you next week at 8:00 p.m. I'll see you next week at 8:00 p.m.
Thank you very much for watching today. Thank you very much.
Koppenpah.